International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft, Lodge 743 Records 1984.0013
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft, Lodge 743 Records
undated, 1900-1983
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1984.0013
33 Linear Feet
Chartered in 1941 to represent members of the International Association of Machinists at Hamilton Standard in East Hartford, Connecticut. In 1952, it moved to Windsor Locks, Connecticut.
History
District Lodge 91, which oversees Lodge activity in Eastern Connecticut.
Local 743 has had several problems with management in its time. The first occurred in 1946 when the union went out on strike over seniority and grievance rights. The strike was unsuccessful, however, and only lasted for a few days. President of the local at that time was Thomas Lynch. In 1960, the union went out on strike for nine weeks over work grievance procedures, union power, job security, and seniority. The president of the local during this strike was Butler Siedman.
During its history, the union has appealed numerous times to the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) when it believed United Aircraft/United Technologies Company was bargaining in bad faith. In the early 1970s, the union appealed to the NLRB, but before the hearing was scheduled, United Aircraft transferred the Broadbrook facility to Composite Materials Corporation, a subsidiary of American Aluminum Company (ALCOA). In 1976, Composite Materials Corporation declined to renew its lease with United Aircraft Company. At this time, United Aircraft closed its Broadbrook facility and moved its production to the Windsor Locks Electronic buildings.
Scope and Content
general administrative records, include job descriptions, employee service ratings, and union membership application cards, Legal files (restricted), contract proposals, meeting minutes, and drafts of agreements, final agreements, correspondence, publications.
Arrangement
Series I: Administrative Files (undated, 1950-1981) contains subject files, arranged in alphabetical order, of the union's general administrative records. Topics include financial records, census reports, conference notes, District correspondence, education and training programs, Executive Board minutes, Grande Lodge activities, and various other materials relating to the daily functions of the local.
Series II: Membership Records (undated, 1950-1982) consists of records maintained by the United Aircraft Company and Local 743. These include job descriptions, employee service ratings, and union membership application cards. Employee service ratings are computer- printed listings of active employees, provided monthly by the company to the union as stipulated by the union contract. They are listed alphabetically by name of employee, by clock number, or by department number. The ratings provide important data on the production workforce, including race, sex, employment and promotion dates, pay grades, etc. The more recent years also note union membership. (Hamilton Standard does not provide union memberships, and union members are marked by hand at the union office.) Archives staff took a one-month (December) sample per year of available records.
Series III: Grievances (1960-1979) consists of three subseries. RESTRICTED FILES
A. Individual Grievances (1962-1979) contain grievances filed alphabetically by name of the grievant. This subseries is restricted.
B. Subject Files (1966-1970) contains grievances filed under subject headings, such as holiday pay, lay-offs, merit rating, termination, contract violations, and working conditions. Also included are administrative records pertaining to grievance procedures containing mostly minutes of company-union grievance hearings.
C. Grievance Steps (1960-1979) make up the majority of the series. The subseries divides grievances into second, third, and fourth steps. Beginning in 1975, the local filed grievances by year and number.
Series IV: Arbitrations (undated, 1954-1979) consists of three subseries.RESTRICTED FILES
A. Opinions and Awards (undated, 1954-1979) contain court decisions and awards for each arbitration case in Loca 743's arbitration file. Also included are awards and decisions from other locals that were used by Local 743 in preparing arbitration briefs.
B. Hearings (undated, 954-1964) contain the daily court proceedings of the arbitration cases.
C. Subjects (undated, 1959-1978) contain briefs, petitions, meeting minutes, notes, and correspondence relating to arbitration cases.
Series V: Contracts And Negotiations (undated, 1953-1981) consists of negotiation sessions, contract proposals, meeting minutes, and drafts of agreements between Local 743 and United Aircraft/United Technologies Company.
Series VI: Agreements (undated, 1941-1983) contains bound copies of agreements between Local 743 and Hamilton Standard Division of United Aircraft/United Technologies Company. Also included are agreements negotiated by Local 743 with Accessory Control Company (1968-77) and Flight Enterprises Company (1959).
Series VII: Court Cases (1952-1978) is the largest series consisting of seven subseries. Subseries F. contains RESTRICTED FILES.
A. State Court Cases (1960-1969) contains court transcripts from United States District Court of Appeals and Hartford County Superior Court.
B. Civil Court Cases (1961-1968) contains transcripts of civil suits brought by the union against United Aircraft and United Aircraft against the union following the 1960 strike, principally 1-CA-9084-9085 and 133844-133885.
C. NLRB Correspondence (1963-1968) consists of correspondence between union representatives and the NLRB pertaining to cases before the Board.
D. NLRB Cases (1955-1976) contains transcripts of cases argued before the Board by Local 743 and United Aircraft Company.
E. Arbitration Subject Files (1960-1974) contains general information relating to various arbitration issues such as job codes, employee rosters, legal correspondence, NLRB rulings, layoffs, employment records, and withdrawal cards.
F. Arbitration, Individual Cases (1959-1978) consists of arbitration cases filed under the grievant's name in alphabetical order. These cases were utilized by union attorneys in various court cases to document unfair labor practices. This subseries is restricted.
G. Contracts and Negotiations (1952-1976) include minutes of negotiations between the company and union referred to by union attorneys to documents the company's reluctance to bargain in good faith.
Series VIII: Flyers (undated, 1900-1977) contains Local 743 and 1746 newsletters, District 91 IAM flyers, and the New Union News.
Series IX: Broadbrook (1958-1976) consists of Local 743 activities at United Aircraft Company's Boron Filament facilities in Broadbrook, Connecticut. On 16 April 1970, as a result of a certified election conducted by NLRB Local 743 was chosen as the exclusive bargaining representative of Broadbrook employees. Four days after the workers' decision to organize, United Aircraft retracted a previously scheduled salary increase. Efforts by Local 743 to negotiate a new contract were delayed by United Aircraft until 1972. After six months of negotiations, Local 743 filed charges with the NLRB that United Aircraft was not bargaining in good faith. Before a hearing could be scheduled, ownership of the Broadbrook facility was transferred from United Aircraft to Composite Materials Corporation (CMC), a subsidiary of American Aluminum Company (ALCOA). As a leasor of the Broadbrook facility, CMC refused to recognize the union and on 11 March 1974 filed a petition with NLRB challenging the union's majority status. Following and investigation by the NLRB on 11 September 1974, CMC voluntarily withdrew its petition and recognized Local 743 as the sole bargaining agent of employees at the Broadbrook facility. An agreement was subsequently negotiated by Local 743 and CMC on 9 September 1974. In 1976, CMC declined to renew its lease and returned the Broadbrook facility to United Aircraft Company. United Aircraft discontinued all operations in Broadbrook and transferred production to its Windsor Electronics 3 building.
The Broadbrook series consists of five subseries.
A. Correspondence (1974-1976), contains correspondence between Composite Materials Company and Local 743.
B. Subject Files (1970-1978) contains agreements, membership list, employee records, newsclippings, and job evaluation data.
C. Negotiations (1971-1976) contains negotiations between Local 743 and United Aircraft and beginning in 1973, negotiations between Local 743 and Composite Materials Company. Also included is a copy of a 1974 agreement between Composite Materials Company and Local 743.
D. Flyers (undated, 1957-1960, 1966) contain flyers and newsletters printed by Local 743.
Series X: Accessory Controls Company (1959-1978), consists of two subseries.
A. Subject Files (1959-1978) contain a variety of topics including correspondence, court cases, contract materials, grievances, job descriptions, meeting minutes, negotiation forms, research reports, and employee records.
B. Negotiations and Agreements (1959-1978) contains negotiations minutes, proposals by the company and the union, and agreements between Local 743 and Accessory Controls Company.
Series XI: Local 2126 (1958-1961) consists of a single subject file that includes correspondence, financial records, and agreements. Local 2126 represents aircraft maintenance workers employed by International Aircraft Services, Inc., Bradley Field Division, Windsor Locks. Local 2126 is affiliated with District Lodge 91 and the International Association of Machinists for the purpose of collective bargaining as of 25 October 1958. The Local's administrative and financial records are maintained by Local 743.
Acquisition Information
The records of Lodge 743 were deposited with the Connecticut Labor Archives at the University of Connecticut on 4 April 1984.
Access
The collection is open and available for research with the exception of Series III, Grievances, and Series VII, Court Cases, which contain confidential and personal material; these series have restricted access and are open only to Lodge #743 officers.
Legal documents; Fliers (printed matter); Monographs; Press releases; Labor unions; Financial Records; Administrative records; Blueprints (reprographic copies).; Membership lists
- Series I: Administrative Files, undated, 1950-1981
  - Accessory Controls Company, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    (see also Series X)
  - Alcoholic Anonymous, 1955-1968 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1972 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1953-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration: recall nights, 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Audit report; local lodges, 1950-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 7-11)
  - Banks, 1959-1962 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Bonding, 1960-1966 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Brief and transcript of Raymond Picard, 1950 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Broadbrook: labor grade 12, 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - By-laws, 1955 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - By-laws, 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - By-laws, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Census report, 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Civil rights, 1964 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - "Club nine", 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Composite Materials Company, correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, 1977-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1975-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - Contract, 1961, 1975 (Box 1:, Folder 26-27)
  - Dance, 1975 April 19 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
  - Deposition: Frederic Gelsi, Broadbrook Plant meeting, 1974 April 1 (Box 2:, Folder 29)
  - District 91, business representative
    - John K. Main, 1959-1962 (Box 2:, Folder 30)
    - John R. Sullivan, 1962-1964 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Robert Nelson, 1968 (Box 2:, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 33-36)
  - Secretary Treasurer Lawrence Brown, undated (Box 2:, Folder 37)
  - District 100, Miami, Florida: IAM flyers, 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 38)
  - Donations: requests, 1974-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 39)
  - Donations: strike, 1974-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 40-43)
  - Drop-outs, 1963-1965 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Dues deductions, 1959-1976 (Box 2:, Folder 45-46)
  - Dues deductions: Accessory Controls Co., undated (Box 3:, Folder 47)
  - Dues increase, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 48)
  - Dues: monthly membership and per capita tax report, 1960 (Box 3:, Folder 49)
  - Eastern Airlines, 1973-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 50-51)
  - Education bulletin kit, 1978 (Box 3:, Folder 52)
  - Elections, Lodge 743, Hamilton Standard, 1956 (Box 3:, Folder 53)
  - Elections, local lodges, 1976-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 54)
  - Election material, 1979-1981 (Box 3:, Folder 55)
  - Excusals from work and leaves of absence, 1977-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 56)
  - Executive Board D-91 meeting minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 3:, Folder 57)
  - Executive Board D-100 meeting minutes, 1981 (Box 3:, Folder 58)
  - Executive Board L-743 meeting minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 59-60)
  - Executive Council D-91 meeting minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 3:, Folder 61)
  - Grand Lodge, 1977-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 62)
  - Grand Lodge officers
    - Glover, Eugene (General Secretary Treasurer), 1978-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 63)
    - DeMore, Matthew (General Secretary Treasurer), 1960-1966 (Box 3:, Folder 64)
  - Grievances, 1960-1968 (Box 3:, Folder 65)
  - Hamilton Standard: Bulletins and Memos, 1959 (Box 3:, Folder 66)
  - Hamilton Standard: Plant layout, undated (Box 3:, Folder 67)
  - IAM Constitution
    - 1969 (Box 3:, Folder 68)
    - 1977 January 1 (Box 3:, Folder 69)
    - 1981 (Box 3:, Folder 70)
  - IAM Officers
    - Hayes, Albert J. (International President), 1958-1962 (Box 3:, Folder 71)
    - Huhndorf, Carl (Director of Research), 1967-1969 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - Iaccio, Sal (Vice President), 1978 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
    - Winpisinger, William (International President), 1976-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 74)
  - Insurance Office, 1973 (Box 3:, Folder 75)
  - Internal Revenue, Income Tax Reports (Box 4)
    - Form 990, 1952-1958 (Box 4:, Folder 76)
    - Form 941, 1969-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 77)
  - Internal Revenue, withholding tax, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 78)
  - Job description and classification, 1968 (Box 4:, Folder 79)
  - Job evaluation, 1975-1978 (Box 4:, Folder 80-81)
  - Job write-up code numbers, undated (Box 4:, Folder 82)
  - Kowalski, Frank, U.S. Congress drafts of letters, undated (Box 4:, Folder 83)
  - Labor department, 1960-1964 (Box 4:, Folder 84)
  - Machinists' Non-partisan Political League, 1975-1978 (Box 4:, Folder 85-86)
  - Membership correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 4:, Folder 87)
  - Membership meeting: agenda, minutes, and original notes of Phillip Kohler (L-743), 1959-1965 (Box 4:, Folder 88-92)
  - Membership meeting minutes (L-1746), 1959-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 93-94)
  - Membership meeting notices (L-743), 1959-60 (Box 4:, Folder 95)
  - Membership meeting, special meeting, Broadbrook plant, 1959 (Box 4:, Folder 96)
  - NLRB: case filings and history, 1955 (Box 4:, Folder 97)
  - Negotiations, 1954-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 98-102)
  - Negotiating committee, Pratt and Whitney, 1959 November (Box 5:, Folder 103)
  - New England Conference of Machinists, 1960, 1978-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 104)
  - Newsclippings: "1960 strike", 1960-1967 (Box 5:, Folder 105)
  - New Union News, 1975 March (Box 5:, Folder 106)
  - Organizing drive, 1959 (Box 5:, Folder 107)
  - Organizing Hamilton Standard, 1967 (Box 5:, Folder 108)
  - Pace, 1959-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 109)
  - Part-time employees, 1966-1968 (Box 5:, Folder 110)
  - Part-time employees, temporary, 1966-1967 (Box 5:, Folder 111)
  - Pension benefits: 1960 strikers, 1977 (Box 5:, Folder 112)
  - Proposals, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 113)
  - Proposals and Broadbrook agreement, 1953-1955 (Box 5:, Folder 114)
  - Proposals and opening letter, 1963-1964 (Box 5:, Folder 115)
  - Receipts and disbursements, 1973-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 116)
  - Relocation to New Haven, 1956 (Box 5:, Folder 117)
  - Seidman, Butler, President, Local 743, 1959-1965 (Box 5:, Folder 118)
  - Seniority roster, 1965 (Box 5:, Folder 119)
  - Stewards, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 120)
  - Steward, committeemen and officers, change in, 1974-1976 (Box 5:, Folder 121)
  - Steward (shop) guide, undated (Box 5:, Folder 122)
  - Stewards' roster, Windsor Locks, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 123)
    - Strike, 1960 (Box 5:, Folder 124-125)
    - Benefits, 1960 (Box 5:, Folder 126)
    - Costs, 1960 (Box 5:, Folder 127)
    - Health, welfare, food certificate record, 1960 June - August (Box 5:, Folder 128-130)
    - List: Accessory Controls Company, 1977 June 27 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
    - Plan and roster, 1960 (Box 5:, Folder 132)
    - Settlement Agreement, 1961 June (Box 5:, Folder 133)
  - Testimony: Harry Gravlin, 1967 April 27 (Box 5:, Folder 134-135)
  - Trainee and apprenticeship program, 1965 (Box 5:, Folder 136)
  - Transfer of committee—men and stewards, 1965 (Box 5:, Folder 137)
  - Unemployment compensation cases, 1962 (Box 6:, Folder 138)
  - Unemployment stamps, requests for, 1961-1966 (Box 6:, Folder 139)
  - Unemployment tax (state), 1957-1969 (Box 6:, Folder 140-141)
  - Unemployment tax (federal), 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 142)
  - Unemployment federal tax form 940, 1969-1972 (Box 6:, Folder 143)
  - United Aircraft Company correspondence, Morgan Mooney, 1960-1964 (Box 6:, Folder 144)
  - United Way, 1974 February 11 (Box 6:, Folder 145)
  - Unity material 1-ca-3355 et al., 1950-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 146)
  - Variety show, 1959 (Box 6:, Folder 147)
  - Wages and classifications, 1963-1968 (Box 6:, Folder 148)
  - Withdrawal cards, honorary, 1958-1963 (Box 6:, Folder 149)
  - Zeman, William S., 1955-1962 (Box 6:, Folder 150)
- Series II: Membership Records, undated, 1950-1982
  - Job descriptions: Hamilton Standard, 1951-1970 (Box 7)
  - Job descriptions: Hamilton Standard, 1961-1978 (Box 8)
  - Employee service rating (Box 9)
    - 1966 December 27
    - 1967 December 31
    - 1968 December 31
    - 1970 December 31
    - 1972 December 31
    - 1973 December 31
    - 1974 December 31
    - 1976 December 31
    - 1977 December 31
    - 1978 December 31
    - 1979 December 31 (Box 10)
    - 1981 December 31
    - 1982 December 31
  - Membership application cards (metal card files), 1950-1962 (Box 11-13)
- Series III: Grievances, (1960-1979)
- Series IV: Arbitrations, (undated, 1954-1979)
- Series V: Contracts and Negotiations, undated, 1953-1981
  - Negotiating committees, 1953-1955 (Box 22)
  - Research bulletins, 1953-1958
  - Contract correspondence, 1958-1961
  - Contract proposals, 1959
  - Negotiations, 1960; (2 folders)
  - Contract proposals, 1960
  - Proposed contract changes, 1960
  - Negotiations, 1962; (2 folders)
  - Contract, 1963
  - Proposals, 1968-1969; (2 folders)
  - Minutes, 1969 March 19
  - Agreement, 1969
  - Negotiations index, 1971-1977
  - Negotiations, 1971 November; (5 folders)
  - Negotiations, 1971 November; (9 folders) (Box 23)
  - Negotiations, 1972 March - April; (10 folders)
  - Index to transcripts, 1974
  - Negotiations: notes and support data, 1974
  - Negotiations, 1974 October - November; (4 folders)
  - Agreement, 1975 April (Box 24)
  - Company contract proposal, 1977 June 27
  - Proposal by Company, 1977 July 21
  - Transcripts Index, 1977
  - Negotiations, 1977 October - November; (7 folders)
  - Pratt Whitney meeting notes, 1977 November 12 (Box 25)
  - Negotiations, 1977 November; (11 folders)
  - Negotiations: notes and support data, 1978
  - Contract proposals, 1978 May - August
  - Proposal and wage and COLA notes, 1980
  - Negotiations, 1980 November; (7 folders) (Box 25)
  - Negotiations: notes and support data, 1981
- Series VI: Agreements, undated, 1941-1983
  - Hamilton Standard Propellers Division, 1941 (Box 26)
  - East Hartford, (1 item)
    - 1942-1946, (3 items)
    - 1948-1950, (2 items)
  - Hamilton Standard, Windsor Locks, 1953-1958; (4 items)
    - 1962-1966, (3 items)
    - 1969-1972, (2 items)
    - 1978-1983, (2 items)
  - Hamilton Standard Building 3 Plant, 1969-1975; (2 items)
  - Hamilton Standard, Broadbrook, 1955-1958; (3 items)
    - 1958-1966, (3 items)
  - Accessory Controls Co., Windsor, 1965-1977; (2 items)
  - Pratt Whitney Aircraft
    - East Hartford and Manchester, CT (L1746), 1960-1971
    - unspecified, (5 items)
  - Flight Enterprises, Inc., Bradley Division, 1959 Feb 9
  - Windsor Locks, (1 item)
- Series VII: Court Cases, 1952-1978
  - Subseries A: State Court Cases, 1960-1969
  - Subseries B: Civil Court Cases, 1961-1968
  - Subseries C: NLRB Correspondence, 1963-1968
  - Subseries D: NLRB Cases, 1955-1976
  - Subseries E: Arbitration Subject Files, 1960-1974
  - Subseries F: Arbitation, Individual Cases, 1959-1978
  - Subseries G: Contracts and Negotiations, 1952-1976
- Series VIII: Flyers, undated, 1900-1977
  - Local 743 and 1746 (Box 32)
    (For more recent flyers, contact the curator.)
    - 1950-1955
    - 1951
  - Local 743 and 1746
    - 1953-59
    - 1954-55
    - 1955-56, (2 folders)
    - 1957-60, (2 folders)
    - 1959
    - 1959-60, (3 folders)
    - 1964-65, (2 folders)
    - 1967, (2 folders)
    - 1967-68
    - 1968, (4 folders)
    - 1969, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - 1970, (3 folders)
    - 1971, (2 folders)
    - 1972, (2 folders)
    - 1973
    - 1977
- Series IX: Broadbrook, 1958-1976
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1974-1976
    - 1974-1976, 3 folder (Box 34)
  - Subseries B: Subject Files, 1970-1978
    - Agreements, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Back pay grievance election ballots, 1975 July 10
    - CAPS-CBT, 1974
    - Check-off, 1974 August 10
    - Insurance Benefits, undated
    - Job evaluation plan, 1974
    - Membership list, 1958 (Box 34)
    - NLRB
    - Certification of representation, 1970
    - Proceedings, petitions, and correspondence, 1971-1974
    - Newsclippings (AFL-CIO News), 1972 April
    - Photographs
      - Florence Sidor
      - Cornelius Aberneen
      - IAM-1743 Bargaining Unit, undated
    - Wage proposals, 1976
  - Subseries C: Negotiations, 1971-1976
    - L743-VAC minutes (Box 34)
      - 1971 October
      - 1971 January 17
      - 1971 March 3
      - 1972 January, (2 folders)
      - 1972 February, (4 folders)
      - 1972 March, (3 folders)
      - 1972 May 2
    - Notes
      - 1972 January 20 - 25
      - 1972 February 3 - 29
      - 1972 March 8 - 22
    - L743-CMC Minutes
      - 1974 July 25 - 30
      - 1974 August 8 - 10
      - 1974 September 4 - 6
      - 1976 August 24, December 8 - 20
    - Flyers
      - 1957-60, (2 folders)
      - 1966
- Series X: Accessory Controls Company, 1959-1978
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, 1959-1978
    - Advertising and Newsclippings, 1962 (Box 35)
    - Cash book, 1955-1962
    - Change of status, 1969-1972
    - Civil suit, Windsor Locks Police Department Contract questionnaire, 1969
    - Correspondence, 1959-1978; (6 folders)
    - Court of Common Pleas
    - Dues deductions, 1970-1972, 1976
    - Federal court civil action H77-655, L743 vs. Town of Windsor, 1978
    - Federal Sign & Signal Company, contract, 1968-1971
    - Grievances, 1962-1973
    - Insurance, 1967-1971
    - Job descriptions, 1960-1969; (3 folders)
    - Labor grade, 1970
    - Meeting minutes (Local 1453), 1960
    - Meetings, special, 1970
    - NLRB cases, 1959-1977; (2 folders)
    - Negotiations forms, 1962, 1968-1971
    - Pension plan, 1965
    - Picket duty roster, 1977 June - July
    - Quarterly Reports, 1969
    - Reinstatement of former employees, 1964
    - Research report forms, 1959
    - Safety committee, 1966